(Howard:)I can't believe we're not going.
(Sheldon:)It's okay.
There-there's always WonderCon
in Anaheim.
(Sheldon:)That's just as good.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Penny:)Guys, this is really sad.
(Penny:)And in a different way
than it was 20 minutes ago.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe we wasted all
that time on our Hulk costumes.
(Penny:)What? You were all going as the Hulk?
(Howard:)Not the same Hulk.
(Howard:)Ferrigno, Bana, Norton and Ruffalo.
(Raj:)We would have been the angry green
belles of the masquerade ball.
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-Yeah.
(Penny:)And we're back
to the first kind of sad.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I have the solution
to our Comic-Con problem.
(Sheldon:)We don't need them.